Markazi AD.MC.025
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- A family in their home-garden., December 2016; cuid1498; 12637; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref96_000001_m)
  Women; Obock, Djibouti; Men; Refugees; Children; Digital Photographs; Boys; Girls; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Gardens; Group Portraits
- A family group of three in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1500; 12639; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref98_000001_m)
  Women; Children; Obock, Djibouti; Men; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair
- A family group of four in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1501; 12640; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref99_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Digital Photographs; Children; Women; Niqab; Refugees; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Boys; Facial Hair; Furnishings; Tents; Carpets/Rugs
- A family group of eight in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1502; 12641; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref100_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Children; Refugees; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Boys; Girls; Tents
- A family group of seven in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1503; 12642; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref101_000001_m)
  Digital Photographs; Refugees; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Boys; Girls; Facial Hair
- A seamstress and her family at home., December 2016; cuid1504; 12643; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref102_000001_m)
  Head Covers/Veils; Obock, Djibouti; Men; Women; Children; Refugees; Digital Photographs
- A family group of eight in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1505; 12644; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref103_000001_m)
  Tents; Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Children; Women; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Boys; Girls; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Hats
- A family group of six in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1506; 12645; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref104_000001_m)
  Men; Women; Refugees; Children; Digital Photographs; Obock, Djibouti
- A man sitting between his daughter and wife., December 2016; cuid1507; 12646; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref105_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Women; Digital Photographs; Men; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Tents; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair
- A female-headed household including five children in the camp., December 2016; cuid1508; 12647; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref106_000001_m)
  Digital Photographs; Children; Obock, Djibouti; Refugees; Women; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Group Portraits; Tents
- A Yemeni family in their rented house in Obock town., December 2016; cuid1509; 12648; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref107_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- A Yemeni family with four children in their rented house in Obock town., December 2016; cuid1510; 12649; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref108_000001_m)
  Digital Photographs; Obock, Djibouti; Children; Niqab; Refugees; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Girls; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Carpets/Rugs
- A family of ten in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1511; 12650; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref109_000001_m)
  Women; Children; Obock, Djibouti; Men; Digital Photographs; Refugees
- A woman with her five children., December 2016; cuid1512; 12651; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref110_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Children; Refugees; Women; Niqab; Digital Photographs
- A family of five in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1513; 12652; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref111_000001_m)
  Tents; Women; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Children; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Men; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Carpets/Rugs
- A family in their container home., December 2016; cuid1514; 12653; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref112_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Men; Head Covers/Veils; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Women; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Girls; Children; Boys; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs
- A family group of seven in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1515; 12654; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref113_000001_m)
  Women; Digital Photographs; Obock, Djibouti; Children; Men; Refugees; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Girls; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Hats; Facial Hair; Tents
- A newly married couple in their Markazi home., December 2016; cuid1516; 12655; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref114_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Men; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Women
- A family of six standing in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1517; 12656; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref115_000001_m)
  Women; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Boys; Arabic Writing
- A family group of six sitting in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1518; 12657; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref116_000001_m)
  Men; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Girls; Boys; Tents
- A woman pregnant with twins and her three children., December 2016; cuid1519; 12658; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref117_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Refugees; Children; Digital Photographs; Women
- A family of three in their home., December 2016; cuid1520; 12659; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref118_000001_m)
  Refugees; Women; Digital Photographs; Men; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Boys; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair
- A family including two women and three children in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1521; 12660; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref119_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Digital Photographs; Boys; Girls; Group Portraits
- A former sailor living alone., December 2016; cuid1522; 12661; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref120_000001_m)
  Individual Portraits; Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Digital Photographs; Men
- A family group with four children in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1523; 12662; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref121_000001_m)
  Women; Children; Obock, Djibouti; Men; Tents; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; United Nations
- A family of five in their courtyard., December 2016; cuid1524; 12663; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref122_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Women; Men; Digital Photographs; Girls; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair; Group Portraits
- A family of six whose yard abuts the camp fence., December 2016; cuid1525; 12664; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref123_000001_m)
  Refugees; Men; Children; Digital Photographs; Women; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Boys; Girls; Head Covers/Veils; Facial Hair
- A family of five whose yard abuts the camp fence., December 2016; cuid1526; 12665; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref124_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Children; Head Covers/Veils; Men; Women; Tents; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Girls; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- A single man living alone inside his IKEA container., December 2016; cuid1527; 12666; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref125_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Men; Digital Photographs; Individual Portraits; Refugees
- A family in their courtyard. A girl in the center is holding a cat., December 2016; cuid1528; 12667; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref126_000001_m)
  Cats; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Girls; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Men; Women; Animals
- A family of seven standing outside their tent., December 2016; cuid1529; 12668; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref127_000001_m)
  Men; Women; Obock, Djibouti; Children; Refugees; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Girls; Boys; Regional/National Dress; Tents; Facial Hair
- A family portrait with the father and son wearing traditional Yemeni dress., December 2016; cuid1530; 12669; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref128_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Digital Photographs; Children; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Tents; Facial Hair
- Four men who have formed a household., December 2016; cuid1531; 12670; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref129_000001_m)
  Refugees; Obock, Djibouti; Group Portraits; Men; Digital Photographs
- A woman living alone., December 2016; cuid1533; 12672; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref131_000001_m)
  Animals; Obock, Djibouti; Refugees; Goats; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Digital Photographs; Individual Portraits
- A family inside their motorized rickshaw., December 2016; cuid1534; 12673; Benchallal, Nadia, Ms. (Object AD_MC_025_ref132_000001_m)
  Obock, Djibouti; Children; Women; Refugees; Men; Digital Photographs; Group Portraits; Girls; Boys; Head Covers/Veils; Tents; Transportation; Facial Hair